{
    "subject": "resource/Ra\u00fal_Silva_Henr\u00edquez",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "1999",
    "human_readable": "Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez died in 1999.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9114968776702881,
            "question": "When did Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8358879089355469,
            "question": "In what century did Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7625625133514404,
            "question": "Who was Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6737214922904968,
            "question": "What could have been the causes of Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48576539754867554,
            "question": "What year marked the end of Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4720224440097809,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46762901544570923,
            "question": "Was Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez a prominent figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4426738917827606,
            "question": "Was Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez known for any particular achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4396117925643921,
            "question": "How did Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez's life impact history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3955360949039459,
            "question": "What field was Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez died in 1999.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1281_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez's life impact history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1281_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez known for any particular achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1281_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez a prominent figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1281_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1281_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Ra\u00fal Silva Henr\u00edquez was born in 1907, served as Archbishop of Santiago de Chile from 1961 to 1983, and died on April 9th, 1999."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Raul Silva Henriquez passed away on April 9th, 1999."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}